# PRONIN KIRILL

BLOCKCHAIN AND WEB FULLSTACK EXPERT

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

Toronto, Ontario(ON), M3H 4J1 CANADA +1 604 316 9348 proninkirilll228@gmail.com GitHub: https://github.com/De

### **EDUCATION**

MASTER'S DEGREE | 2012~2016 | UNIVERSITY OF QUEBEC, CANADA ·

Major: Computer Science

Related coursework: Theory of Computation, Fundamentals of Computer Science, Compilers and Operating Systems, Information theory, Basic Programming, Systems and Architecture, Web Applications and Databases, Blockchain and Cryptocurrencies, Algorithms and Data Structures

## **SKILLS & ABILITIES**

**BLOCKCHAIN TECHNOLOGY** ·

Tokenization, Solidity, Haskell, Rust, Layer-2 Development

WEB DEVELOPMENT

React.js/React Native, UI/Unit Testing · Node.js/Express.js, Vue, Angular, Svelte, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Gatsby, Gridsome, Django, Flask, Laravel · HTML5/CSS3, Sass/Less, Java(Spring, Struts), Ruby on Rails, Django, ASP.NET, PHP(Laravel, CI)

**DATABASE** 

NoSQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, SQLite, Firebase, GraphQL

Mohile

Java(Kotlin), Swift - IONIC, React Native, Flutter, Unity, Unreal PROJECT MANAGEMENT Agile Methodology, Azure DevOps, CI/CD, Git, Jira, Trello, Bitbucket

## **PERSONAL SUMMARY**

Senior Software Engineer with 6+ years of experience developing, testing and deploying crypto projects, web services and mobile apps.

Excellent ability to meet deadlines and work as part of a team to deliver great works.

High proficient in object-oriented methodologies, data structures and algorithms, as well as quality coding and excellent debugging skills.

Since I'm a cool hearted person, so usually see every difficulty with a positive side and keep myself always smiling which makes me stronger even more.

I need a platform to prove my ability and will put my effort and strength to uplift your company.

None is born with experience and I will get more professional experience through working.

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Remote 02/2021 - 09/2021

Refinable is a decentralized multi-chain NFT marketplace for users to trade items from across the metaverse.

Discover, Trade, and Create NFTs from the best and upcoming projects and collections on Ethereum, Solana, Binance Smart Chain, and Polygon.

- Built the first biggest NFT Marketplace of digital art on Binance Smart Chain using ERC-721 for single and ERC-1155 for multi NFT and BEP-20 for governance token.
- Developed whole smart contracts from scratch and past the Audit from SlowMist.
- Built token bridge between Binnance and Ethereum so that users are able to migrate their NFTs from ETH to our platform.
- Implemented basic functionalities of NFT marketplace such as sale, auction, airdrop and used proxy for service fee calculation.
- Implemented NFT fractionalization so that users are able to co-won NFT and decide further steps like sale, auction, airdrop together.
- Developed on-chain & off-chain governance protocol with FINE token so that users are able to tomake decision of adding new features and modifying current functionalities of platform
- Key Achievements: NFT Sale, Airdrop, Service Fee, Auction, NFT Fractionalize, NFT Bridge, Governance

### **WORK HISTORY**

#### **RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER**

#### Remote | 01/2020 - 02/2021

Integration new function for CRM to Chatwoot open source project.

Fat-Free CRM functions integrated into chatwoot by using Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Redis and Vue framework.

- Integration API for Vue frontend
- Convert Fat-Free CRM UI to Vue UI,
- Customization of Openproject
- Create Live Chatting room via WebRTC(video, voice and file share function)
- Frontend Design

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### **LEAD SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

## Leb Stupka Travel Company | 2015 - 2018 https://www.suisse-view.ch/

This is the Switzerland Travel company and owner was Leb Stupka.

Virtual Visit System, Wedding Reservation system, Virtual Visit Application. React Native, React, PHP, Node, MySQL, MongoDB, Rest API, Firebase notification, Twilio and AWS server was used.

- Generated Wedding reservation site, Schedule time and paypal and stripe payment integration.
- Generated Travel Booking system and Hotel reservation and booking system
- Virtual Visit System Video Streaming Site
- Android and IOS app development by using React, Firebase

### **WORK HISTORY**

#### **PROJECT MANAGER**

## Quality Circle International 07/2018 - 12/2020 https://qualitycircleint.com/

Built the LMS(Learning Management System) and Risk Tool(Food Quality System) by using PHP. Node, React, Angular, MySQL, MongoDB

- Built the create Exam System and Create Lesson function by using the jQuery and html
- Virtual Lesson system and payment(PayPal and Payoneer) integration for course.
- Schedule the time of course and invite users to the course which is created. Change the schedule and add new.
- Email notification for signup, create course, invite user -
- Course marketing part and advertisement.
  Enrollment for the course and check the exam mark system
- Roll management system for Super admin, Company, Instructor admin and Students.

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

## Multi Vendor Marketing Company | 2013-2014https://supplieson.com

Tensail Analytics provides clients with unprecedented gaming industry expertise combined with a comprehensive customerfocused vision. The combination of the two is unmatched within the gaming service provider marketplace

- Scraped details of sports events, odds, boxscores, match stats, leaderboards from espn, rivals, synergy, stats-ncaa, donbest, pgatour and more.
- Analysed the data contents and made expectation for the future match results.
- Provided expectations with several formats according to the license Kept managing the unmanaged.
- VPS server